<resources>
    <!-- App Name -->
    <string name="app_name">Plate Handler</string>

    <!-- NavigationView Menu -->
    <string name="nv_home">Home</string>
    <string name="nv_recipe">Recipes</string>
    <string name="nv_product">Products</string>
    <string name="nv_shopping">Shopping List</string>
    <string name="nv_export">Export Database</string>
    <string name="nv_import">Import Database</string>
    <string name="nv_credits">Credits</string>

    <!-- Drawer -->
    <string name="dt_opened">Drawer Opened</string>
    <string name="dt_closed">Drawer Closed</string>

    <!-- Dialog -->
    <string name="dg_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="dg_cancel">Cancel</string>

    <!-- Pager -->
    <string name="pg_info">Information</string>
    <string name="pg_ingredient">Ingredients</string>
    <string name="pg_step">Steps</string>

    <!-- Menu Items -->
    <string name="mn_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="mn_share">Share</string>
    <string name="mn_calculate">Calculate</string>
    <string name="mn_edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="mn_remove">Remove</string>

    <!-- Button -->
    <string name="bt_shopping">Create New List</string>
    <string name="bt_ingredient">Add New Ingredient</string>
    <string name="bt_step">Add New Step</string>
    <string name="bt_item">Add New Item</string>
    <string name="bt_recipe">Select Recipe</string>

    <!-- Dialog Message -->
    <string name="dg_pd_add">Do you want to add a new product?</string>
    <string name="dg_pd_edit">Do you want to edit the product?</string>
    <string name="dg_pd_remove">Do you want to remove the product?</string>
    <string name="dg_rp_add">Do you want to add a new recipe?</string>
    <string name="dg_rp_edit">Do you want to edit the recipe?</string>
    <string name="dg_rp_remove">Do you want to remove the recipe?</string>
    <string name="dg_sp_add">Do you want to create a new shopping list?</string>
    <string name="dg_ex_add">Do you want to create a new export file?</string>
    <string name="dg_im_choose">Do you want to import data from this file?
        All your previous data will be removed!</string>

    <!-- SnackBar Message -->
    <string name="sb_pd_add">New product added!</string>
    <string name="sb_pd_edit">Product updated!</string>
    <string name="sb_pd_remove">Product removed!</string>
    <string name="sb_st_add">New step added!</string>
    <string name="sb_rp_add">New recipe added!</string>
    <string name="sb_rp_edit">Recipe updated!</string>
    <string name="sb_rp_remove">Recipe removed!</string>
    <string name="sb_sp_add">New shopping list created!</string>
    <string name="sb_ex_add">Database exported!</string>
    <string name="sb_im_add">Database imported!</string>

    <!-- Toast Message -->
    <string name="ts_welcome">Welcome to Plate Handler!</string>
    <string name="ts_product">Product data is incomplete!</string>
    <string name="ts_used">This product cannot be removed because
        it is used in a recipe!</string>
    <string name="ts_recipe">Recipe data is incomplete!</string>
    <string name="ts_step">Step data is incomplete!</string>
    <string name="ts_shopping">Shopping list data is incomplete!</string>
    <string name="ts_export">Export data is incomplete!</string>
    <string name="ts_item">At least one item is required!</string>
    <string name="ts_database">Database error!</string>
    <string name="ts_file">File operation error!</string>
    <string name="ts_directory">New directory created!</string>
    <string name="ts_empty">At least one product has no set average size!</string>

    <!-- Errors -->
    <string name="er_pd_name">Product name is empty!</string>
    <string name="er_pd_nutrients">Sum of nutrients in product
        cannot be higher than its average size!</string>
    <string name="er_rp_name">Recipe name is empty!</string>
    <string name="er_rp_author">Name of the author is empty!</string>
    <string name="er_ig_amount">Empty amount!</string>
    <string name="er_st_content">Content of this step is empty!</string>
    <string name="er_sp_amount">Empty amount!</string>
    <string name="er_sp_name">Empty name!</string>
    <string name="er_ex_name">Name of the file to export is empty!</string>

    <!-- Empty List -->
    <string name="ep_recent">No recipes shown!</string>
    <string name="ep_recipe">Recipe list is empty!</string>
    <string name="ep_product">Product list is empty!</string>
    <string name="ep_step">Step list is empty!</string>
    <string name="ep_shopping">Shopping list is empty!</string>
    <string name="ep_import">Import file list is empty!</string>
    <string name="ep_spinner">No Products!</string>

    <!-- Finished -->
    <string name="fn_ingredient">Used!</string>
    <string name="fn_step">Done!</string>

    <!-- Captions -->
    <string name="ct_statistics1">Recipe Amount</string>
    <string name="ct_statistics2">Product Amount</string>
    <string name="ct_name">Name</string>
    <string name="ct_author">Author</string>
    <string name="ct_serving">Servings</string>
    <string name="ct_time">Time</string>
    <string name="ct_difficulty">Difficulty</string>
    <string name="ct_spiciness">Spiciness</string>
    <string name="ct_country">Cuisine</string>
    <string name="ct_type">Type</string>
    <string name="ct_preference">Preferences</string>
    <string name="ct_meat">Meat</string>
    <string name="ct_vegetarian">Vegetarian</string>
    <string name="ct_alphabetical">Alphabetically</string>
    <string name="ct_favorite">Favorite</string>
    <string name="ct_measure">Measure</string>
    <string name="ct_amount">Amount</string>
    <string name="ct_product">Product</string>
    <string name="ct_step">Step</string>
    <string name="ct_size">Average Size</string>
    <string name="ct_carbohydrates">Carbohydrates</string>
    <string name="ct_proteins">Proteins</string>
    <string name="ct_fats">Fats</string>
    <string name="ct_nutrients">All Nutrients</string>
    <string name="ct_date">Shopping Date</string>
    <string name="ct_state">Shopping State</string>
    <string name="ct_other">Other</string>
    <string name="ct_chart">Percentage Charts of Nutrients</string>
    <string name="ct_total">Total Calories</string>
    <string name="ct_per">Per Serving</string>
    <string name="ct_developer">Developer</string>
    <string name="ct_version">Version</string>
    <string name="ct_license">License</string>
    <string name="ct_attribution">Attribution</string>
    <string name="ct_saved">Saved Data</string>
    <string name="ct_unsaved">Unsaved Data</string>

    <!-- Export -->
    <string name="ex_recipe">All Recipes</string>
    <string name="ex_product">All Products</string>
    <string name="ex_shopping">Shopping List</string>
    <string name="ex_settings">All Settings</string>
    <string name="ex_photo">All Photos</string>

    <!-- Header -->
    <string name="hd_hm_statistics">App Statistics</string>
    <string name="hd_hm_recent">Recently Shown Recipes</string>
    <string name="hd_rp_mg_photo">Set Recipe Photo</string>
    <string name="hd_rp_mg_essential">Set Recipe Essentials</string>
    <string name="hd_rp_mg_data">Set Recipe Data</string>
    <string name="hd_rp_sh_data">Recipe Data</string>
    <string name="hd_rp_sh_ingredient">Ingredients</string>
    <string name="hd_rp_sh_step">Preparation Steps</string>
    <string name="hd_rp_cl_kcal">Recipe Calories (Kcal)</string>
    <string name="hd_rp_cl_kj">Recipe Calories (Kj)</string>
    <string name="hd_rp_cl_ingredient">Ingredient Calories</string>
    <string name="hd_rp_settings">Recipe Searching Settings</string>
    <string name="hd_ig_mg_add">Add Ingredient</string>
    <string name="hd_ig_mg_data">Set Ingredient Data</string>
    <string name="hd_st_mg_add">Add Step</string>
    <string name="hd_st_mg_current">Current Steps</string>
    <string name="hd_st_mg_data">Set Step Content</string>
    <string name="hd_pd_mg_photo">Set Product Photo</string>
    <string name="hd_pd_mg_essential">Set Product Essentials</string>
    <string name="hd_pd_mg_composition">Set Product Composition</string>
    <string name="hd_pd_sh_composition">Product Composition</string>
    <string name="hd_pd_sh_kcal">Product Calories (Kcal)</string>
    <string name="hd_pd_sh_kj">Product Calories (Kj)</string>
    <string name="hd_pd_settings">Product Searching Settings</string>
    <string name="hd_sp_sh_data">Shopping List Data</string>
    <string name="hd_sp_sh_list">Shopping List</string>
    <string name="hd_sp_mg_add">Add Shopping Item</string>
    <string name="hd_sp_mg_data">Set Shopping Item Data</string>
    <string name="hd_ex_data">Set Export File Name</string>
    <string name="hd_ex_guideline">Export Guidelines</string>
    <string name="hd_im_file">Import Files</string>
    <string name="hd_cd_author">Author of the App</string>
    <string name="hd_cd_library">Libraries Used</string>
    <string name="hd_cd_icon">Icons Used</string>
    <string name="hd_cd_font">Fonts Used</string>

    <!-- Tutorial -->
    <string name="tt_hm_statistics">A section presenting the user with statistics regarding the
        database used in the <b>Plate Handler</b> app.\n\nThe fragment <b>Recipe Number</b>
        defines the number of recipes added by the author, while <b>Product Number</b> expresses
        the sum of all saved products and those added by default to the database after the first
        launch of the app.</string>
    <string name="tt_hm_recent">A section showing a list of <b>six</b> recently viewed recipes
        available in the app.\n\nThe individual items are ordered <b>from the last
        shown</b> recipe. Choosing one of them takes the user to a specific page of the recipe.
    </string>
    <string name="tt_rp_mg_photo">A section allowing the user to add a photo representing the
        <b>approximate appearance</b> of the currently created recipe. It is not a required part of
        the creation process to be completed.\n\nThe user can select a specific image from the
        gallery by selecting <b>the button on the left side</b>. If the photo does not meet the
        requirements, it can be removed using <b>the button on the right side</b>.</string>
    <string name="tt_rp_mg_essential">A section allowing the user to supplement
        <b>main data</b> regarding the recipe. It is a required part to be completed and
        <b>cannot be left empty</b>.\n\nThe <b>Name</b> text field stands for the name given to the
        recipe, while <b>Author</b> text field describes the creator of a particular dish.</string>
    <string name="tt_rp_mg_data">A section allowing the user to specify information about the
        recipe, allowing <b>easier identification</b> of dishes among other functions. Data is set
        here using various types of <b>control views</b>.\n\nIn the <b>Servings</b> fragment, the
        user can increase or decrease the number of portions allocated in the recipe by using the
        <b>plus and minus buttons</b>.\n\nThe <b>Time</b> fragment informs about the time period of
        preparation of the recipe, which is set by clicking the <b>special button</b>
        (<b>cannot</b> be equal to zero minutes).\n\nThe <b>Difficulty</b> and <b>Spiciness</b>
        fragments contain progress bars through which the user can increase the level of
        difficulty of the recipe and how spicy the dish is.\n\nThe drop-down views appearing in
        <b>Cuisine</b> and <b>Type</b> fragments allow user to choose the country from which the
        recipe comes from and in which category it belongs.\n\nThe last fragment named
        <b>Preferences</b> allows the user to select the item representing the preferences in terms
        of composition of the recipe, depending on whether it contains meat or is vegetarian.
    </string>
    <string name="tt_rp_sh_data">A section presenting the user with <b>main information</b>
        regarding the selected recipe.\n\nThe <b>Servings</b> fragment represents the number of
        portions allocated in the recipe, the <b>Time</b> fragment shows how much time is needed
        to prepare the dish, while <b>Difficulty</b> expresses the level of difficulty of the
        recipe.\n\nThe spiciness of the dish is represented by icons in the <b>Spiciness</b>
        section. One pepper means a <b>mild</b> dish, while four peppers mean a <b>super hot</b>
        one.\n\nThe <b>Cuisine</b>, <b>Type</b> and <b>Preferences</b> fragments characterize the
        country from which the recipe comes from, which category it falls in and whether it is
        vegetarian or not in that order. In addition, this data is marked with matching
        <b>icons</b>.</string>
    <string name="tt_rp_sh_ingredient">A section showing a list of <b>ingredients</b> included in
        a selected recipe. Each item contains basic information about a specific ingredient,
        consistent with those set at the stage of recipe creation.\n\nAt the top of the specific
        item is the <b>name</b> of the product used as the ingredient, <b>the quantity combined
        with the measure</b> of the ingredient is located below it, and on the left there is the
        icon representing the <b>type</b> of the product.\n\nIn the <b>upper right corner</b> of
        each ingredient there is a <b>checkbox</b>, which after being clicked informs the user
        about <b>ingredient being used</b> while executing the recipe.</string>
    <string name="tt_rp_sh_step">A section showing a list of <b>preparation steps</b> of the
        recipe. Each item contains basic information about a specific step, in line with those
        set at the stage of creating the recipe.\n\nAt the top of the specific item there is the
        <b>number</b> of the step representing the order in which steps should be followed, and
        below it the <b>content</b> in the form of instructions to follow is located.\n\nIn
        the <b>upper right corner</b> of each step there is a <b>checkbox</b>, which after being
        clicked informs the user about <b>completing the given step</b> while executing the recipe.
    </string>
    <string name="tt_rp_cl_kcal">A section presenting information about <b>total amount of
        calories</b> in a selected recipe to the user, expressed in <b>kilocalories</b>. All
        calorific values of individual ingredients have been summed up here.\n\nThe
        <b>Total Calories</b> fragment determines the total amount of calories in a given recipe,
        while <b>Per Serving</b> fragment expresses the number of calories allocated to <b>exactly
        one portion</b> of a given meal.\n\nIf at least <b>one product</b> belonging to an
        ingredient does not have its information about composition set, the caloric data
        <b>will be empty</b>.</string>
    <string name="tt_rp_cl_kj">A section presenting information about <b>total amount of
        calories</b> in a selected recipe to the user, expressed in <b>kilojoules</b>. All
        calorific values of individual ingredients have been summed up here.\n\nThe
        <b>Total Calories</b> fragment determines the total amount of calories in a given recipe,
        while <b>Per Serving</b> fragment expresses the number of calories allocated to <b>exactly
        one portion</b> of a given meal.\n\nIf at least <b>one product</b> belonging to an
        ingredient does not have its information about composition set, the caloric data
        <b>will be empty</b>.</string>
    <string name="tt_rp_cl_ingredient">A section showing a list of <b>ingredients</b> for a
        selected recipe, along with their calories. With this solution, the user can find out
        exactly what values are included in the summed up calorie composition of the entire
        recipe.\n\nEach individual item contains <b>basic information</b> about a specific
        ingredient, consistent with that available on the recipe page.\n\n<b>The left side</b>
        of each item shows the <b>calorific value</b> of the ingredient, expressed in both
        <b>kilocalories</b> and <b>kilojoules</b>. If the composition information has not been
        set in the product used in the ingredient, the calorie data <b>will be empty</b>.</string>
    <string name="tt_rp_settings">A section allowing the user to specify <b>search settings</b>
        regarding recipe selection. Individual changes are made here by using the <b>switches</b>,
        available in every fragment.\n\nIf the user selects a switch in the <b>Alphabetical</b>
        fragment, then the list of recipes will be displayed in alphabetical order.\n\nBy clicking
        the switch in the <b>Favorite</b> fragment, a restriction is introduced so that only
        recipes <b>marked with a star</b> are visible.\n\nAfter selecting the switch in the
        <b>subsequent fragments</b> <b>the drop-down views</b> will appear for setting
        further restrictions on recipe searching.\n\nIf the user wants to lift the restrictions on
        displayed items, the specific switches need to be <b>unchecked</b>.</string>
    <string name="tt_ig_mg_add">A section allowing the user to add new items to set data for
        individual <b>ingredients in a recipe</b>.\n\nThe user can increase the number of items by
        clicking the <b>Add New Ingredient</b> button. The following items will appear in the list
        in the <b>Set Ingredient Data</b> section down below.</string>
    <string name="tt_ig_mg_data">A section allowing the user to specify information about
        individual ingredients of a recipe. Data is set here using various types of
        <b>control views</b> available for each item.\n\nThe <b>Amount</b> text field signifies a
        number representing the quantity of a specific ingredient with a certain measure, which is
        required to correctly complete the dish. Its value must be <b>greater than zero</b>.\n\nIn
        the <b>Measure</b> fragment, the drop-down view allows the user to choose the correct
        measure of the ingredient.\n\nDepending on whether <b>there are products</b> in the
        app, the <b>Product</b> fragment may contain a drop-down view that allows the
        user to select an available product as a part of the ingredient in the recipe. The
        following items <b>cannot use</b> the same product repeatedly.\n\nThe <b>plus</b> button
        located on the <b>right side</b> of each item allows the user to add a new product if the
        required element <b>does not exist</b> in the drop-down view. By clicking it the user
        will open the product creation page.\n\nOn <b>the left side</b> of each item there is a
        <b>cross out icon</b>, which will delete the item after clicking it.</string>
    <string name="tt_st_mg_add">A section that allows the user to add new <b>recipe preparation
        steps</b>.\n\nThe user can increase the number of items by clicking the <b>Add New Step</b>
        button, and a new page will open. After completing certain information, subsequent items
        will appear in the list in the <b>Current Steps</b> section down below.</string>
    <string name="tt_st_mg_current">A section showing a list of previously added <b>steps</b> of
        the recipe. If a specific step does not meet the requirements, it can be changed
        here.\n\nIn the <b>upper right corner</b> of each step there is a <b>cross out icon</b> and
        by clicking it the user will delete the following item.\n\nNext to it <b>on the left</b>
        is the <b>edit</b> button that allows the user to change the content of the selected
        step.\n\nIf <b> no steps are added</b>, the list will be empty.</string>
    <string name="tt_st_mg_data">A section allowing the user to complete <b>the content</b>
        regarding a specific step of the recipe. It is a required part to be completed and
        <b>cannot be left empty</b>.\n\nThe <b>Step</b> text field signyfies a detailed description
        of the instructions required to complete the recipe at a given stage.</string>
    <string name="tt_pd_mg_photo">A section allowing the user to add a photo representing the
        <b>approximate appearance</b> of the currently created product. It is not a required part
        of the creation process to be completed.\n\nThe user can select a specific image from the
        gallery by selecting <b>the button on the left side</b>. If the photo does not meet the
        requirements, it can be removed using <b>the button on the right side</b>.</string>
    <string name="tt_pd_mg_essential">A section allowing the user to set <b>primary data </b> of
        the product.\n\nThe <b>Name</b> text field indicates the name given to the product. It is
        a required part to be completed and <b>cannot be left empty</b>.\n\nThe <b>Type</b>
        fragment contains a drop-down view that allows the user to choose the category of the
        product.</string>
    <string name="tt_pd_mg_composition">A section allowing the user to specify
        <b>composition values</b> of the product. The <b>text fields may remain empty</b>,
        however, this prevents the app from calculating calories for both the product and the
        recipe in which it was used.\n\nThe <b>Average Size</b> text field specifies the average
        total weight of a particular product, while <b>Carbohydrates</b>, <b>Proteins</b> and
        <b>Fats</b> fields characterize the amount of nutrients the product includes (their sum
        <b>must not exceed</b> the total size). The unit of each value depends on the previously
        set <b>type</b> of the product (<b>grams</b> or <b>milliliters</b>).</string>
    <string name="tt_pd_sh_composition">A section presenting the user with information about the
        <b>composition</b> of a given product, expressed in <b>grams</b> or <b>milliliters</b>
        (depending on the <b>product type</b>).\n\nThe <b>Carbohydrates</b>, <b>Proteins</b> and
        <b>Fats</b> fragments determine the nutrient values of the product, while the <b>Other</b>
        fragment expresses the remaining composition, obtained after subtracting nutrient values
        from total weight.\n\nIn the <b>Percentage Charts of Nutrients</b> fragment there are two
        charts - <b>bar chart</b> shows the percentage values of each nutrient separately, while
        the <b>pie chart</b> presents the percentage values of the sum of all the nutrients
        compared to the remaining composition of the product.\n\nIf composition data of the
        product has not been set, the calorific data <b>will be empty</b>.</string>
    <string name="tt_pd_sh_kcal">A section presenting the user with information about
        <b>calories</b> in a selected product, expressed in <b>kilocalories</b>.\n\nThe
        <b>Carbohydrates</b>, <b>Proteins</b> and <b>Fats</b> fragments specify the calorific
        values for individual nutrients in the product, while the <b>Total Calories</b> expresses
        the sum of all calorific values of the product. \n\nIf composition data of the
        product has not been set, the calorific data <b>will be empty</b>.</string>
    <string name="tt_pd_sh_kj">A section presenting the user with information about
        <b>calories</b> in a selected product, expressed in <b>kilojoules</b>.\n\nThe
        <b>Carbohydrates</b>, <b>Proteins</b> and <b>Fats</b> fragments specify the calorific
        values for individual nutrients in the product, while the <b>Total Calories</b> expresses
        the sum of all calorific values of the product. \n\nIf composition data of the
        product has not been set, the calorific data <b>will be empty</b>.</string>
    <string name="tt_pd_settings">A section allowing the user to specify <b>search settings</b>
        regarding product selection. Individual changes are made here by using the <b>switches</b>,
        available in every fragment.\n\nIf the user selects a switch in the <b>Alphabetical</b>
        fragment, then the list of products will be displayed in alphabetical order.\n\nAfter
        selecting the switch in the <b>Type</b> fragment, a <b>drop-down view</b> will appear for
        setting a search restriction based on selected type of the product.\n\nIf the user wants to
        lift the restrictions on displayed items, the specific switches need to be
        <b>unchecked</b>.</string>
    <string name="tt_sp_sh_data">A section presenting the user with information about the current
        <b>shopping list</b>. If the shopping list does not exist, <b>data will be
        empty</b>.\n\nThe <b>Shopping Date</b> fragment specifies the exact day the shopping list
        was created, while the <b>Shopping State</b> expresses how many shopping items were
        crossed out from the list.\n\nThe user can create a new shopping list by clicking the
        <b>Create New List</b> button, and the list creation view will open.</string>
    <string name="tt_sp_sh_list">A section presenting a shopping list with <b>items placed one
        after the other</b>. They can be <b>crossed out</b> by clicking them, so the user do not
        have to remember what items are already bought.\n\nIf the user has crossed out an item by
        mistake, the error can be fixed by <b>clicking the item again</b>.</string>
    <string name="tt_sp_mg_add">A section allowing the user to add new elements to set data for
        individual <b>shopping list items</b>.\n\nThe user can increase the number of items by
        clicking the <b>Add New Item</b> button. The following items will appear in the list
        in the <b>Set Shopping Item Data</b> section down below.\n\nTo ensure user convenience,
        there is an option to immediately add <b>all ingredients</b> of a specific recipe as
        shopping list items by clicking the <b>Choose Recipe</b> button and selecting the
        appropriate recipe in the newly opened view.</string>
    <string name="tt_sp_mg_data">A section allowing the user to specify information about
        individual items of the shopping list. Data setting is done here using the various
        <b>control view</b> available for each of the items.\n\nThe <b>Amount</b> text field
        indicates a number representing the quantity of a specific item to buy with a certain
        measure. Its value must be <b>greater than zero</b>.\n\nIn the <b>Measure</b> fragment,
        the drop-down view allows the user to select the correct measure for the shopping list
        element.\n\nIn the <b>Name</b> text field, the entered value is the name of the shopping
        list item and <b>cannot be left empty</b>.\n\nOn <b>the left side</b> of each item, there
        is a <b>cross out icon</b>, which removes the item after clicking it.</string>
    <string name="tt_ex_data">A section allowing the user to specify a <b>name</b> of the file
        containing exported database from the app. This data is a required part to be
        completed and <b>cannot be left empty</b>.\n\nThis value must be entered in the <b>Name</b>
        text field. Appending the file extension name to the end <b>is unnecessary</b>, by default
        it will be set as <b>xls</b> after the export operation is completed.</string>
    <string name="tt_ex_guideline">A section presenting guidelines to the user regarding saving the
        database in the form of an <b>export file</b>. Some parts of data
        <b>will be omitted</b>.\n\nThe <b>Saved Data</b> fragment specifies exactly what data
        groups will be saved in the generated xls file, while the <b>Unsaved Data</b> fragment
        lists the information, which will be unsaved and deleted from the app after the
        <b>import operation</b> is completed.</string>
    <string name="tt_im_file">A section showing a list of files created as part of the
        <b>export operation</b>. They contain specific information from the database of the
        app and are used to import said data.\n\nFor each item, <b>the number of recipes
        and products</b> it contains is determined. After selecting a specific file,
        <b>import operation</b> is performed, which involves deleting the current data of
        the app.</string>
    <string name="tt_cd_author">A section presenting the user with information about the author of
        the <b>Plate Handler</b> app.\n\nThe <b>Developer</b> fragment contains the
        name, surname and nickname of the author. Information about <b>libraries and icon</b> used
        by the creator of the app can be found in the sections below.</string>
    <string name="tt_cd_library">A section showing a list of libraries used in the
        <b>Plate Handler</b> app. Each item contains basic information about a
        particular library, starting with its <b>name</b> at the top of the item.\n\nThe
        <b>Author</b> fragment defines who the author of the library is, the <b>Version</b>
        fragment expresses the identifier of the library version used in the app, while the
        <b>License</b> fragment describes which license covers each library.</string>
    <string name="tt_cd_icon">A section showing a list of packs with icons used in the
        <b>Plate Handler</b> app. Each item contains basic information about a
        particular pack, starting with its <b>name</b> at the top of the item.\n\nThe
        <b>Attribution</b> fragment shows the exact contents of the attribution about the author
        of the icon pack, the <b>License</b> fragment describes what license the package is
        covered by, while the <b>Amount</b> fragment determines the number of icons from the given
        pack used in the app.</string>
    <string name="tt_cd_font">A section showing a list of fonts used in the logo and the icon of
        the <b>Plate Handler</b> app. Each item contains basic information about a
        particular font, starting with its <b>name</b> at the top of the item.\n\nThe
        <b>Author</b> fragment defines who the author of the font is, the <b>Version</b>
        fragment expresses the identifier of the font version used in the logo and the icon of
        the app, while the <b>License</b> fragment describes which license covers each
        font.</string>

    <!-- Main Toolbar Titles -->
    <string name="tb_hm_welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="tb_rp_choose">Choose Recipe</string>
    <string name="tb_rp_settings">Recipe Settings</string>
    <string name="tb_rp_add">Add Recipe</string>
    <string name="tb_rp_show">Recipe</string>
    <string name="tb_rp_edit">Edit Recipe</string>
    <string name="tb_rp_calculate">Calculate Calories</string>
    <string name="tb_st_add">Add Step</string>
    <string name="tb_st_edit">Edit Step</string>
    <string name="tb_pd_choose">Choose Product</string>
    <string name="tb_pd_settings">Product Settings</string>
    <string name="tb_pd_add">Add Product</string>
    <string name="tb_pd_show">Product</string>
    <string name="tb_pd_edit">Edit Product</string>
    <string name="tb_sp_show">Shopping List</string>
    <string name="tb_sp_add">Create Shopping List</string>
    <string name="tb_ex_database">Export Database</string>
    <string name="tb_im_database">Import Database</string>
    <string name="tb_cd_show">Credits</string>

    <!-- Content Description -->
    <string name="dp_logo">Logo of the app</string>
    <string name="dp_pd_photo">Image of the product</string>
    <string name="dp_pd_type">Icon of the product type</string>
    <string name="dp_rp_photo">Image of the recipe</string>
    <string name="dp_rp_spiciness">Icon of the recipe spiciness</string>
    <string name="dp_rp_type">Icon of the recipe type</string>
    <string name="dp_rp_country">Icon of the recipe country</string>
    <string name="dp_rp_preference">Icon of the recipe preference</string>
    <string name="dp_expand">Icon representing expandable view</string>
    <string name="dp_caption">Icon of the caption</string>
    <string name="dp_side">Icon on the side of the item</string>
    <string name="dp_remove">Option to remove the item</string>
    <string name="dp_dot">Icon of the shopping item</string>
    <string name="dp_tutorial">Icon of the tutorial option</string>
    <string name="dp_bt_add">Button to add a photo</string>
    <string name="dp_bt_remove">Button to remove a photo</string>
    <string name="dp_bt_plus">Button to increase number of servings</string>
    <string name="dp_bt_minus">Button to decrease number of servings</string>
    <string name="dp_bt_time">Button to set time of the recipe</string>
    <string name="dp_bt_edit">Button to edit the item</string>
    <string name="dp_bt_product">Button to add the new product</string>

    <!-- Array Text Difficulty -->
    <string name="ar_df_easy">Easy</string>
    <string name="ar_df_medium">Medium</string>
    <string name="ar_df_hard">Hard</string>

    <!-- Array Text Spiciness -->
    <string name="ar_sp_mild">Mild</string>
    <string name="ar_sp_medium">Medium</string>
    <string name="ar_sp_hot">Hot</string>
    <string name="ar_sp_extra">Extra Hot</string>

    <!-- Array Text Preference -->
    <string name="ar_pf_vegetarian">Vegetarian</string>
    <string name="ar_pf_meat">Meat</string>

    <!-- Array Text Country -->
    <string name="ar_ct_american">American</string>
    <string name="ar_ct_austrian">Austrian</string>
    <string name="ar_ct_brazilian">Brazilian</string>
    <string name="ar_ct_british">British</string>
    <string name="ar_ct_bulgarian">Bulgarian</string>
    <string name="ar_ct_chinese">Chinese</string>
    <string name="ar_ct_croatian">Croatian</string>
    <string name="ar_ct_czech">Czech</string>
    <string name="ar_ct_french">French</string>
    <string name="ar_ct_georgian">Georgian</string>
    <string name="ar_ct_german">German</string>
    <string name="ar_ct_greek">Greek</string>
    <string name="ar_ct_indian">Indian</string>
    <string name="ar_ct_italian">Italian</string>
    <string name="ar_ct_japanese">Japanese</string>
    <string name="ar_ct_mexican">Mexican</string>
    <string name="ar_ct_moroccan">Moroccan</string>
    <string name="ar_ct_polish">Polish</string>
    <string name="ar_ct_portuguese">Portuguese</string>
    <string name="ar_ct_russian">Russian</string>
    <string name="ar_ct_south_korean">South Korean</string>
    <string name="ar_ct_spanish">Spanish</string>
    <string name="ar_ct_thai">Thai</string>
    <string name="ar_ct_turkish">Turkish</string>
    <string name="ar_ct_ukrainian">Ukrainian</string>
    <string name="ar_ct_vietnamese">Vietnamese</string>
    <string name="ar_ct_other">Other</string>

    <!-- Array Text Recipe -->
    <string name="ar_rp_breakfast">Breakfast</string>
    <string name="ar_rp_appetiser">Appetiser</string>
    <string name="ar_rp_drink">Drink</string>
    <string name="ar_rp_soup">Soup</string>
    <string name="ar_rp_dinner">Dinner</string>
    <string name="ar_rp_salad">Salad</string>
    <string name="ar_rp_sauce">Sauce</string>
    <string name="ar_rp_spice">Spice</string>
    <string name="ar_rp_dessert">Dessert</string>
    <string name="ar_rp_other">Other</string>

    <!-- Array Text Product -->
    <string name="ar_pd_grain">Grain</string>
    <string name="ar_pd_bread">Bread</string>
    <string name="ar_pd_dairy">Dairy</string>
    <string name="ar_pd_fat">Fat</string>
    <string name="ar_pd_egg">Egg</string>
    <string name="ar_pd_vegetable">Vegetable</string>
    <string name="ar_pd_fruit">Fruit</string>
    <string name="ar_pd_meat">Meat</string>
    <string name="ar_pd_fish">Fish</string>
    <string name="ar_pd_seafood">Seafood</string>
    <string name="ar_pd_pasta">Pasta</string>
    <string name="ar_pd_spice">Spice</string>
    <string name="ar_pd_liquid">Liquid</string>
    <string name="ar_pd_sauce">Sauce</string>
    <string name="ar_pd_other">Other</string>

    <!-- Array Text Measure -->
    <string name="ar_ms_piece">Piece</string>
    <string name="ar_ms_gram">Gram</string>
    <string name="ar_ms_decagram">Decagram</string>
    <string name="ar_ms_kilogram">Kilogram</string>
    <string name="ar_ms_millilitre">Millilitre</string>
    <string name="ar_ms_litre">Litre</string>
    <string name="ar_ms_teaspoon">Teaspoon</string>
    <string name="ar_ms_tablespoon">Tablespoon</string>
    <string name="ar_ms_cup">Cup</string>

    <!-- Default Products -->
    <string name="df_tomato">Tomato</string>
    <string name="df_carrot">Carrot</string>
    <string name="df_onion">Onion</string>
    <string name="df_bread">Rye Bread</string>
    <string name="df_grain">Whole Grain Bread</string>
    <string name="df_gouda">Gouda Cheese</string>
    <string name="df_cow">Cow Milk</string>
    <string name="df_breast">Chicken Breast</string>
    <string name="df_egg">Chicken Egg</string>
    <string name="df_lemon">Lemon</string>
    <string name="df_salt">Salt</string>
    <string name="df_pepper">Pepper</string>
    <string name="df_ketchup">Ketchup</string>
    <string name="df_mayonnaise">Mayonnaise</string>
    <string name="df_butter">Butter</string>
    <string name="df_sugar">Sugar</string>
    <string name="df_garlic">Clove of Garlic</string>
    <string name="df_red">Red Pepper</string>
    <string name="df_juice">Orange Juice</string>
    <string name="df_tenderloin">Beef Tenderloin</string>
    <string name="df_pork">Minced Pork</string>
    <string name="df_cod">Cod</string>
    <string name="df_trout">Trout</string>
    <string name="df_parsley">Parsley</string>
    <string name="df_celery">Celery</string>
    <string name="df_wheat">Wheat Flour</string>
    <string name="df_rye">Rye Flour</string>
    <string name="df_cream">Cream 18%</string>
    <string name="df_yogurt">Natural Yogurt</string>
    <string name="df_buckwheat">Buckwheat</string>
    <string name="df_rice">White Rice</string>
    <string name="df_pasta">Pasta Noodles</string>
    <string name="df_oil">Rapeseed Oil</string>
    <string name="df_orange">Orange</string>
    <string name="df_apple">Apple</string>
    <string name="df_broccoli">Broccoli</string>
    <string name="df_toast">Toasted Bread</string>
    <string name="df_spaghetti">Spaghetti Noodles</string>
    <string name="df_tagliatelle">Tagliatelle</string>
    <string name="df_lard">Lard</string>
    <string name="df_corn">Corn</string>
    <string name="df_peas">Peas</string>
    <string name="df_cucumber">Cucumber</string>
    <string name="df_sweet">Sweet Paprika</string>
    <string name="df_hot">Hot Paprika</string>
    <string name="df_gyros">Gyros</string>
    <string name="df_curry">Curry</string>
    <string name="df_mustard">Mustard</string>
    <string name="df_shrimp">Shrimp</string>
    <string name="df_squid">Squid</string>
</resources>